Excuse me, sir. Sir, is this your Ferrari?
Yeah.
And how did you get a Ferrari?
I grew it to 17 million dollars,
asking successful people how they made it.
What did you do for a living?
I built a point-of-sales device that
I sold to Cisco Food Systems.
You sold a company to Cisco?
Yeah.
For how much money?
A little north of 70 million.
70 million dollars?
I've built and sold five other companies since then.
You just have more than 10 million dollars?
Who, me?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah. That's tiny. You don't
stay in business making 10 million dollars.
I built a satellite company.
What was the most amount of
money you made in a year?
We won one contract for billions
of dollars from the U.S. government,
because we were the early guys.
You built a billion-dollar company?
Yeah.
Congratulations, man.
Excuse me, sir. Question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Oh, God.
Well, that's an interesting question.
I had a misspent youth, so
it took longer than you'd expect.
What was your turning point to financial freedom?
I was a farm boy from Illinois.
I became a plastic surgeon here in Silicon Valley.
What's the best industry to get into right now?
Nobody's talking about it.
Give me the best industry.
That's a tough one.
I think if there's one lesson about business,
you would instill in the people watching right now
that is not taught in school,
what would that be?
This is Silicon Valley,
the place that has created more billionaires
than anywhere else on Earth.
It's home to the biggest companies,
the boldest ideas,
and the richest people alive.
Trillions of dollars of innovation started right here.
Today, I'm doing something insane.
I flew all the way out to California
to interview some of the most powerful
and wealthiest entrepreneurs in the entire world.
The billionaires who literally built the future
from tech founders,
to venture capital giants.
These are the people who changed the world
and got filthy rich doing it.
So today, I'm gonna be
figuring out their billionaire secrets
on how they built their wealth
and how you watching can become financially free
going into 2026.
Now, this video is about to
be insane from start to finish,
so stay tuned until the end.
With that being said, let's
get this video on the way.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, how old were you when you became a millionaire?
Oh, I'm really sorry.
We're just not doing any press, but thank you.
Oh, okay.
So real quick, I have
a channel with 17 million followers.
I'm really sorry.
We're going.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, I got a question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Uh, you're not doing that.
Yeah?
Real quick.
So I grew a channel to 17.
I actually have to get to a meeting right now.
Okay.
So thank you though.
One lesson to the younger generation.
Excuse me, sir.
Sir, how old were you when you became a millionaire?
Hey, real quick, sir.
Sir, I got a channel with.
I'm not taking pictures.
I'm not taking any videos.
Excuse me, sir.
Yeah.
Question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
I'm good.
I appreciate you guys doing your thing.
I appreciate you, man.
Appreciate you, man.
Excuse me, ma'am.
Question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Yeah.
Wait.
Real quick.
I grew a channel to 17 million followers.
I interviewed business owners on their advice
to the younger generation.
I know.
Sorry.
Thank you.
All right, you guys.
As you can see, it is literally impossible.
It's not possible.
It's impossible to get these people to stop and talk,
let alone get some advice for you all.
I mean, there's like 75 billionaires that live out here.
So some of these rich
people out here, they're private, man.
They do not want to give it away.
But I didn't come out here for nothing.
I'm going to do whatever it
takes to get these people to stop
and talk and get a million dollars,
scratch that, a billion dollars
worth of gain for you all.
So come with me.
Let's go see who we can find.
Come on.
Sir, question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
What?
I have no freaking clue.
What line of business are you in?
Venture capital.
Why?
I grew a channel to 17 million followers.
I go all over the world interviewing successful people
to help the younger generation.
I've interviewed 25 billionaires in the last four years.
Could I get one minute with you real quick?
No.
But thank you.
Two questions.
Somebody's trying to raise money for their business.
What's the number one thing that you
look for in a founder that tells you,
I'm going to give my money to them?
Market opportunity.
And what is the best opportunity in today's world?
Anything to do with AI.
AI?
It can change everything.
Would you say that if you're not
using AI, you're going to get it?
You are so good.
Seriously.
Well, let me ask you.
Would you say that?
What school did you go to?
University of Texas.
But I did.
Oh, you went to Michigan.
What happened?
Would you say if you're not using AI,
you're going to get left behind?
Yes, definitely.
So how would you be leveraging AI in your business?
Let me ask you.
I thought you said one minute.
You're past your time.
No, this isn't a minute.
You're funny, but I like you.
I promise you.
This is to help the younger people.
I've done Tom Cruise, Tom Brady, Mark Cuban, Reid Hoffman.
Good for you, though.
Some of your friends probably.
What's the best financial advice you ever received
throughout your career from a mentor?
Listen to the customer.
Yeah?
Is it customers or employees first?
Customer.
Why?
Always the customer.
Now, you're in VC.
Customer doesn't buy.
You don't have a business.
Are you raising or are you investing in businesses?
Is it invest?
Real quick, did you ever?
Real quick, sir, last one.
It's competitive in VC.
How are you getting money from other people?
You've got to have a track record.
Yeah?
You've got to prove to them
that you can make money for them.
What's the best investment you
ever made throughout your career?
Commerce One.
What's that?
What type of company was that?
Long before you were probably born.
So what is the big issue
you had in terms of revenue?
Not personal income, just revenue.
Venture guys don't talk like that.
An idea of revenue.
Was it more than $10 million?
Who, me?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
That's tiny.
You don't stay in business making $10 million.
Look, Arch, you guys.
So I tried to squeeze as
much game out of that guy
as I possibly could.
He's a VC out here.
You could tell, man, he looked like money.
And even though I couldn't get most out of him,
I was trying to be persistent.
But the one takeaway that I had was two.
He said, you've got to
be using AI in your businesses.
The second thing is your customer comes first in business.
You need to understand that.
If you take care of your customer,
everything takes care of itself.
So solid interview out here.
We've got to go get this next one, you guys.
Come on.
Excuse me, sir.
Question for you.
How old were you when you became a millionaire?
Oh, .
I was 21.
How did you get rich?
Like, what allowed you to do this?
I built a point of sales
device that I sold to Cisco Food
Systems.
You sold a company to Cisco?
Yeah.
For how much money?
A little north of $70 million.
$70 million?
Yeah.
And what was the biggest
thing that led to that exit?
Fit and function.
Because we only actually made $60,000 in revenue.
And we spent $17 million on the company.
And so we were in
the rears probably about, I mean,
basically $17 million.
But it was fit and function.
They had 11,000 sales reps.
And they needed certain things.
And next thing you know,
it kind of just worked out.
And we figured out that the
process of them hiring another 9,000 sales
reps was probably worth about $70 to $80 million.
So we landed on a number.
And we went from there.
So it's safe to say then price
is only an issue if value is absent.
Because you were able to present the, hey,
even though you're going to
buy my company for $70 million,
you're going to save so
much more money than I want.
Value is only in the eye of the beholder.
I've built and sold five other companies since then.
Are you serious?
Yeah.
And been a part of things.
I mean, she's the CEO of a company
right now that literally is going from $5
million to $50 million to $300 million next year.
What was the biggest company you exited?
Was it that one right there?
No.
The biggest company was another business.
I can't say.
But it was about $285 million.
You exited for $285?
And what's the biggest one going to be?
Mine?
Well, actually, the biggest one, no.
I'm not even joking.
And that was all technology business.
I built and sold one to Facebook,
built and sold one to NetSuite slash Oracle.
And a lot of stuff.
What was your turning point to entrepreneurship?
OK.
So you're talking to a kid that didn't
learn how to read till he was in ninth
grade and has no parents.
And so really just my high
school senior project was a business.
And I ended up, my grandmother, who I didn't really
know till I was 18 years
old, gave me a $70,000 check.
And.
Next thing you know, I gave her money
back in three months and built my first
magazine and just kind of figured out
I'm just going to work for myself because
I'm probably not normally hireable.
Now, we're in Silicon Valley right now.
We're going into 2026.
What is the best industry people should
be looking to get into right now in
today's world?
You know, it's funny, man.
I have built a lot of software companies.
I built a cannabis business.
I'm in the energy and
infrastructure space more now and manufacturing.
So, for example, so Alyssa, she
owns a company called Butcher Power Products.
Siemens, ABB, some of the
largest companies in the world that
make billions and billions of dollars to build switchgear.
Switchgear sounds like it's not hard to do.
Amazon put out a study last year that said
that if they ate up all of the capacity of
switchgear in the United States for
manufacturing over the next 10 years,
they'd only be at 25% of what they needed.
That's one company.
There's also Facebook.
There's a bunch of other ones.
So right now, I diversified and went
into the switchgear space, invested in there,
looked at it, invest my time, energy,
my people, everything else I have into that
space.
And it's sort of a,
I would say, low technology space.
It's been around for 30, 40, 50 years.
The reality is Siemens, ABB, LS.
All these other players do billions and billions of dollars.
But there's so many orders in that
space that you can't keep up with volume.
We have the capacity to do
about a billion two in revenue.
And we get to choose our clientele.
We do about 50% margins on everything we do.
So I'm getting software money out of freaking manufacturing.
So you see like energy manufacturing.
It's been an interesting space.
And switchgear is this giant stupid
box that basically takes the low, medium,
high voltage that comes from power lines.
Like this building has a bunch of switchgear.
Probably this building alone is
$15 million worth of switchgear.
So the more building you're doing,
the more you're building.
The reality is the entire industry
is 30, 40, 50 years old.
So you have to replace all the old stuff.
Plus there's a bunch of new.
Data centers take anywhere from, a small
data center will take $15 to $20 million
worth of switchgear.
A large one will take a billion.
Did you have anybody that doubted you?
Everybody.
Everybody?
I mean, I couldn't read
until I was in ninth grade.
So I doubted myself.
What was the number one book that changed your life?
The Bible.
So you believe in God?
Oh, absolutely.
Somebody doesn't believe in God right now.
What would your message be to them?
Factually, you're wrong.
I studied Christian apologetics at
Stanford University for about a year.
The reality is a design creator is a fact.
It's not fiction.
I would say go look at yourself in the mirror.
Every designer has to have a creator.
This is the funniest thing, right?
So there's this belief that something
bigger than you is divine and
doing something in the universe.
And at some point when you die,
you're gonna be in a place
with a thing that's bigger than you.
That's the largest religion in America.
And the reality is, is that's just Christianity.
Right. Right.
And if you look at it,
the reason why I always tell people,
like at the end of the
day for me, it's always been Christianity.
It's the only religion in the
world in which it's nothing you do.
No offense, you're not important, I'm not
important, she isn't, none of us are.
It's the reality of what God did for
us to bring us there because
I'm imperfect and so are you.
So if I'm imperfect, I can't go to
a perfect place and live in a perfect place
and be a part of it because what happens?
It becomes imperfect.
Jesus is key.
Amen. I love it.
You got amazing advice, sir.
Thank you so much for
your time and I appreciate you.
That guy just gave a crazy interview.
And look, he said he sold four or
five companies and one for over $280 million.
He sold a company to Facebook.
But I need you to listen
to me very carefully right now.
Look, 99% of people will never get
the chance to be mentored from a millionaire
or a billionaire.
They might watch them on YouTube and videos
like this or podcasts, but they never get
the chance to ask them a question directly.
That's why I built the greatest
entrepreneur community in the entire world.
And I'm not kidding.
It's called the School of Mentors.
Inside every single week, I bring
in the same multimillionaires and billionaire entrepreneurs
that you see on this channel.
And instead of the millionaires and billionaires just
talking to me, they mentor you live on
Zoom every single week.
You literally get to raise your
hand and ask them your questions.
Ask them questions about your business or how
to build wealth and get real answers from
people who've already built eight,
nine, and even 10 bigger businesses.
Now here's the craziest part.
You're watching this right now.
And for Black Friday,
you're doing something absolutely insane.
To celebrate, we're giving you 50% off so
you can get access to the School of Mentors
for just $25.
This isn't a $10,000 mastermind or a $1,000 course.
This is real proximity to real entrepreneurs
and real mentors that have built real business.
And I'm not kidding.
I'm not kidding.
I'm sure you'll hit 50% off.
Because thank goodness, we have our 100th
number of young entrepreneurs in the actually
done business.
But here's the catch.
Look, this Black Friday offer is
strictly limited for the next 48 hours.
Once it's gone, the price goes back up.
So if you're watching this right now, and
you've ever wanted actual access to the eight, nine,
and 10 figure entrepreneurs, the billionaires that
you see me interview on this channel,
this is your sign.
All you have to do is go down, click the
link in the description of this video to grab your
spot for just $25, and I'll see you
inside of the number one entrepreneur community and
network in the entire world.
With that being said, let's go get this next interview.
Well, that does end our discussion today.
interview. Excuse me sir. Sir. Is this your
Ferrari? Yeah. And how did you get a Ferrari?
I grew it up to 17 million followers
asking successful people how they made it. What did
you do for a living? I worked at Apple. You worked
at Apple? Yeah. What were you doing at Apple? I was
an engineering director. Let me ask you this. How did
you work your way up at Apple? It's a very
competitive company. What did you do to stand out?
Did a great job. You did a great job. So
can you build real wealth working in the corporate
world? It's not easy. Not easy? Actually this is
more accidental than anything else. What do you mean?
You invest and all of a sudden it takes off.
What did you invest in primarily? What was
your vehicle? Apple. Apple stock. You bet. How long
were you at Apple for? Oh gosh. Almost 20 years.
20 years? So back in the early 2000s. Before that.
In the 1990s? Yeah. So what made you decide to
go work with Apple early on before all the you know?
It was the only place that you could do the
great great work that we did. Almost 20 years. What's
the best industry people should be looking to get
into right now in today's world? I honestly don't
know. I mean everyone's in the AI bandwagon
which means that it's probably not the best.
It's not the best place to be. I look
at the contrary version. Actually. So you think that
when too many people are talking about something then
you want to go to the other way. Yeah. So
what are you looking at? What's that thing for
you right now? I can't tell you right now. Everybody
would run in. What did you study
in college? Political science. Political science. How'd you
end up working for a tech company? Oh that's a
long story. Tell me. How'd you get into the tech
industry? I gotta go. Okay. Thanks. All right.
Last one. Last message to the younger generation.
Your last message to help them stand out
and become a millionaire in today's world. Oh invest
your time wisely and find something you love. Did
you ever start your own business? I did. Yeah?
But no. I think doing what
we did at Apple there's no other
place on earth you could do that. Why? What
do they do differently from everybody else? Look at
the product line. I will tell you. What
makes them so successful? What's a lesson from Apple
that other young entrepreneurs can learn today as well?
Set a high bar. Set a high bar. Do they
think a lot bigger? Yeah. Always try to
elevate what you're doing. What types of companies did
you start? Well same same kind of thing as a
tech thing. The lesson I learned at Apple is always set
a high bar. Yeah. You know everybody's trying to
do the best job they can. That's how you get
great products out of it. Thank you so much
for your time sir. I appreciate you. You got great
advice. Really appreciate your time. Thank you sir. Thank
you. So I go up to my guy in the
Ferrari and he didn't make his wealth starting
businesses but he was an employee at Apple. An
early employee at Apple in the 1990s and it just
goes to show if you're in the right place at the
right time you can still become rich. I mean he's
Ferrari rich you guys so he got there for a reason.
Pretty cool interview out here in Silicon Valley in
the tech capital of the world. Let's go get
another one you guys. Come on. Excuse me sir.
Sir. How old were you when you became a millionaire?
How when I? Yeah. How old were you? I
can't remember. It was so long ago. No I'm kidding.
Could have been 50. So you made
it later in life. Yeah. Was delayed gratification
important? Yeah.
Patients in your career? It was okay. Yeah. And
how did you get rich? What line of business are
you in? I built a satellite company. A
satellite company? But that's such a niche business. How
did you get into building satellites? I found a
company that was broken. It was after 9-11 and
I thought we're going to need more information
about people around the world and I had lost
a friend on 9-11. Sorry for your loss. So it
was more like let's fix this and find this kind of
information that we need more of. I didn't realize until
I'd been at it for a while that we'd make a
ton of money. Right. What was the most
amount of money you made in a year? Oh
we won one contract for billions of dollars from
the US government because we were the early guys.
So you built a billion dollar company?
Yeah. Congratulations man. How did you get that
contract? I got a, I want to make sure my
Uber doesn't leave. You know what they won't. Let me
talk to them. I have a channel with
17 million followers. I've interviewed 25 billionaires in
the last four years to help the younger generation. Let
me ask you this. If you could give me one piece
of advice on how you scaled out a multi-billion
dollar company. How did you do that? It takes a
lot of work and a lot of commitment. You have to
work six days a week or seven and you have to be
lucky. Did you sacrifice? Did you sacrifice? Did
you sacrifice? Did you sacrifice? Did you sacrifice?
Oh yeah, sure. I worked six or seven days a
week for years. When you found the company. Didn't get
to see my son's football games and stuff
like that. But we made America safer. We protected
the environment. We created lots of jobs and we
made our investors rich. So it was like the
American dream. How did you sell to the US
government? How did you land? We went in and
said you need to know more about the world.
This is so long ago that people didn't have digital
maps. A friend of mine started Google
Earth. Nobody believed they needed digital maps. You
guys grew up with maps in your phone but back
then they didn't have them. So we convinced people you
need to know more about the world. So we convinced
people you need to know more about the world. So
we convinced people you need to know more
about the world. So I really got to go.
I don't know people that thought
you were crazy when you were buying.
Totally. They said go back to, you know, I built
it in Washington. They said go back to New York.
Digital mapping. Nobody will ever make
money. Why didn't you listen to them?
I was convinced it would work and that
was the crazy part. I stuck with it.
Thank you so much for your time.
So I appreciate it. Wait, real quick,
sir. You said it was broken. What did you go
in there to fix it? What's the most common mistake,
the most common reason why
businesses are broken in today's world?
They are selling what they
have, not what the customer needs.
You're a good negotiator.
A great negotiator. But sell the customer
what they need, not what you have.
If you solve needs, you're going to get rich.
What's the best advice you ever got from a mentor?
One lesson that a mentor taught you that always
don't give up. Yeah. Did you almost give up?
No, but it was crazy to keep going.
Last message to the younger generation right here. One
more nugget to them to build a billion dollar
company, man. One more lesson to the younger generation.
Work hard, but be excited. The future is
so bright. You all ought to be wearing shades.
2026. What's the best industry to get into
right now? Nobody's talking about. Give me the best
industry. That's a tough one. That's a tough
question. I think cyber is going to be hugely
important. Why? Because AI is making
it easier to fake everybody out.
My God.
I founded a satellite company of all businesses,
you guys, and he just gave us an incredible
interview out here in Silicon Valley. We
have all businesses, satellites, built a multi-billion
dollar business and just gave us a great
interview, you guys. Come on, man. Silicon Valley's going
crazy. Excuse me, sir. Question for you. How
old were you when you became a millionaire?
Oh, God.
I know these guys out here.
Oh, do you? Well, that's an
interesting question. I had a misspent youth,
so it took longer than you'd expected.
And how did you make it, would you say?
I'm a plastic surgeon. I just worked hard.
So you got to visit a plastic surgeon.
I made my patients happy and
they rewarded me and it was great.
So when you came out of medical school,
what was your turning point to building your own
practice and having your own business?
I think I knew from the beginning
I wanted to be a plastic surgeon.
Why?
So it was great. I wanted to
make people happy and I wanted to see
everyone enjoying it. So it
was a great field for me.
Did you learn that the
more happy you make other people,
the more money you're going to make in turn?
I think it works out that way.
Yeah.
I don't know if I learned it that way.
I don't want to say that, but it definitely happens.
I became a plastic surgeon because I wanted to
be an orthopod because this orthopod guy was really,
I wanted to be a sports doctor. And then this plastic
surgeon, I was like, I want to be a sports doctor.
Yeah.
Then this plastic surgeon showed up in
some pink gargoyle glasses and he was like,
you need to come with me and become a
plastic surgeon. And he converted me and it all worked
out great.
I'm going to challenge you. Take me back
to the most life-changing conversation you ever had.
What's the best advice you ever
got from a mentor throughout your career?
That's a good question.
That was one of them because he told me just to
be you and enjoy it. And I think, I'm old. I mean,
I see so many young people. You can
drive into the drive-through at McDonald's, right? And meet
someone who you can just see them and
you're like, they're going to be something someday.
And everyone can be something someday. And I became,
I was a farmer. I was
a farmer. I was a farmer.
I was a farm boy from Illinois. I
became a plastic surgeon here in Silicon Valley.
What do most medical professionals get wrong about
the business side of medicine? Because a lot of
them, they come out of school, they've got shiny
objects in them when they get out because they're
in school for so damn long. When you come
out of school, what's a way that you could advise
them about building the business the right way?
I think for any business and when
you create happiness for yourself and happiness for
everyone around you, you will succeed. I have people
come into me and give me $20,000 in cash
for their surgery that are ditch diggers, that
own businesses that worked really hard. And when you
enjoy what you're doing, you're good
at it. You're going to be successful.
You can succeed.
Have you seen the business of medicine
change a lot, especially in plastic surgery?
Where do you think it's going?
Oh, it's evolved a lot
for sure. It's evolved a ton.
And have you adapted a lot
of the technology that's came out?
The technology has been great for sure. It's
improved what we do. It's improved how our
patients improve. It's been great. Plastic
surgery has been a really wonderful field.
Why?
Because it's just evolved. Our results are better.
People heal faster. People are happy. I mean,
all you'd have to do is come to work with me
for a day. You can bring that camera around and you
would see so many people so happy.
A lot of people are judgmental about plastic
surgery. I think that's a good thing. I think
that's a good thing. I think that's a good thing.
A lot of people think it's vain
or it's superficial, but people are super happy.
And you can make millions in that space as well.
You can make money, but you can also, I
mean, I would argue that the happiness is more than
the money.
I love that. You got amazing advice, sir. Thank
you so much for your time. And I appreciate you,
man. This is great.
All right, you guys, that is a wrap on
today's video. I need you to like and subscribe for
amazing content, man. We just came out to one
of the richest cities on planet earth, Silicon Valley,
to figure out how they got rich and how you can
do the exact same thing. But let's go a step further,
you guys. See, I launched and built
the number one most powerful entrepreneur community in
the entire world where every single week you
can get mentored directly from the millionaires and
the billionaires I interview on this channel. So
if you want direct access to the millionaires
and billionaires I interview and you want them to
mentor you, go down, click the link in the
description of this video to join the school of
mentors today. I can't wait to see you on
the inside. With that being said,
I'll see you in the next video.